You are not worth adding to our squad.
What is he...
Rage of Bahamut
痛ぇ…｡ あっ))
They are the same
and lose themselves
Cuz there are lots of roads to go
And the path suddenly seems rougher
I wanna walk straight ahead
Knock down another dream
(隊長)((貴様には
隊に入れるほどの価値はない))
Most broke before they ever came true
But walk this way
Get out of my way
Depends on the way you think it
To a yielding heart
the future, hope,
despair and worry all look all the same
So much that you'll turn down the truth
that lied to you that day
when you were prepared for it all.
You go your way, don't you?
(ﾌｧﾊﾞﾛ･ﾚｵｰﾈ)あいつ…｡
But walk this way
Get out of my way
You're all clean now.
(ﾘﾀ)
うん これで きれいになったわ｡
ザァーー…
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)残念だ｡
It was a terrible shame.
Was it not them?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)あいつらではないのか？➡
ここを知る者で いないのは
貴様の部下だけだ｡
The only ones who know of this place
who aren't here are your subordinates.
ディアスとアレサンドを
疑うのか？
Are you accusing Dias and Alessand?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)ヤツらは ｼｬﾘｵｽの犬だった｡
違う！
They were Charioce's dogs.
-No!
-Then tell me!
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
ならば ムガロを殺したのは誰だ!?
Who killed Mugaro?
分からない！
しかし 彼らは私の協力者だ｡
I don't know!
But they are my allies!
Then are you saying that one of us did it?
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)では この中に
犯人がいるとでも言うのか？
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)そんなことは言っていない！
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)なら 認めろ！
-I'm not saying that!
-Then accept it!
貴様が おめおめと犬を引き入れ
ムガロを殺したのだ｡
You roped those dogs into this
and got Mugaro killed!
それ以上の侮辱は許さぬぞ！
ぐっ！
I will not tolerate any more insults!
≫(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)やめろ バカ野郎！
Stop it, you idiots!
≫(ﾆｰﾅ･ﾄﾞﾗﾝｺﾞ)
あっ あっ… ああっ…➡
あのガキを殺したのは
アレサンドだ｡
The one who killed the kid
was Alessand.
それは… 本当なのか？
Is that
really true?
ああ｡
逃げていくのを この目で見た｡
Yeah.
I saw him running away
with my own eyes.
You'll see it's true if you just
look into it enough.
調べりゃ いずれ分かることだ｡
シャリオスともども
ぶっ殺してやる｡
I'll kill him and Charioce!
ジャンヌさん｡
Jeanne!
We're returning to the land of the gods.
(ｿﾌｨｴﾙ)神界に戻る｡
I've killed the holy child!
聖なる子供を殺しました｡ はぁ…｡
我々の敵
聖なる子供を やったんです｡
I killed our enemy, the holy child.
この手柄で
俺を 漆黒兵に入れてください｡➡
Please let me join the Onyx Soldiers
as a reward for this feat!
はぁ はぁ…｡
ついてこい｡
Come with me.
ごほっ ごほっ！ ごほっ！
To join our unit, you will need
this stone implanted in your chest.
我が隊に入るなら
これを胸に埋め込んでもらう｡➡
These stones feed on our life force
この石は 命を食らう｡
それにより我らは 力を得る｡➡
and grant us power in return.
We offer our lives to execute our orders.
命をささげ 任務を遂行する｡
That is what our unit does.
それが 我が部隊だ｡
あ… あの～ 俺 その…➡
Uh, well...
I...
命を懸けるとか
そ… そんなの知らなくて…｡
I didn't know I'd have to risk my life.
(隊長)ｵﾙﾚｱﾝ騎士団は くれてやる｡
えっ？
I'll put you in charge of the Orleans Knights.
(隊長)それで満足しろ｡
≪コツ コツ コツ…
You should be satisfied with that.
カァー カァー…
ダン！
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)あのバカ者！ くっ｡
That fool!
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)ジャンヌ様とアザゼルは➡
Jeanne and Azazel are thinking
that Alessand was an assassin sent by His Majesty.
アレサンドが 陛下による
刺客であったと考えている｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)バカな！
陛下が アレサンドなどに➡
Impossible!
His Majesty would never entrust
Alessand with such an important mission!
そんな大役を
任せるはずありません！
私も そう思う｡
I don't think so either.
単独犯でしょう｡
He most likely did it on his own.
何故 あのバカ者は
そんなまねを…｡
But why would he do something so stupid?
分からない｡
I don't know.
結局 私には➡
In the end,
I was never able to understand
アレサンドが
何を考えていたのか➡
理解することができなかった｡
what Alessand was thinking.
ジャンヌ様の動向は？
Where did Jeanne go?
She's returned to the land of the gods.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)神の国へと向かった｡
おそらくは➡
It's likely that she's gone to raise support
for a retaliation against His Majesty.
陛下へと行動を起こすのに
協力を得るためだろう｡
アザゼルも
何をしでかすか分からない｡
And I don't know what Azazel might do.
また
戦いになるかもしれませんな｡
This may mean another battle.
陛下は まだ城に？
昨晩 秘密裏に城を発ちました｡
Is His Majesty still at the castle?
He left the castle in secret last night.
この時期にか？ 一体 どこへ…｡
At a time like this?
Where could he have gone?
エイボスです｡
To Eibos.
How did you get that information?
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)その情報 どうやって？
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)
重臣の一人を脅し 吐かせました｡
I threatened one of the chief vassals
and pried it out of him.
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)危険なまねを…｡
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)おかげで もう➡
That was dangerous.
On account of it, I won't be able to
return to the castle.
城には戻れません｡
これ以上の争いを防ぐために
協力してくれるか？
Will you work together to
prevent further conflict?
That's always been my intention.
もとより そのつもりです｡
おしっ！
All right!
こ～んな場所でも
やっぱ きれいな方がいいよね｡
Even a place like this would be
better clean.
ムガロちゃん なんか 私ね➡
Mugaro.
Seems like I can't get sad.
悲しくならないの｡
Maybe so many sad things
happened
悲しいことばっかりだったから
私の心➡
おかしくなっちったのかなぁ｡
that something broke inside me.
Rage of Bahamut
≫(ﾘﾄﾞ)ガブリエル様！➡
Lady Gabriel!
ソフィエル様が戻られました｡
Lady Sofiel has returned.
El has been killed.
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)エルが殺されました｡
(ｶﾞﾌﾞﾘｴﾙ)あっ｡
シャリオス１７世を討伐します➡
I will bring down Charioce XVII.
This I swear.
必ず｡
You are going to help me.
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)協力してもらいます｡
私の命 そなたに託す｡
I offer my life to you.
人は 人の手で討つ！
A man shall fall with the hands of a man!
バシッ！
ザシュ！
(魔族)待て！
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)どけ｡
-Stop!
-Out of my way.
It's been a long time,
(ﾙｼﾌｪﾙ)久しぶりだね アザゼル｡
Azazel.
ルシフェル様
今こそ アナティ進軍のときです｡
Lucifer.
The time has come to march on Anatae.
突然 どうしたんだい？
Where is this suddenly coming from?
先の戦いの被害が残る今➡
While they are still reeling
from the previous battle
全魔族の
総力を挙げれば 押し切れます｡
we will be able to push through
if we send everything we have.
それに 間もなく
人の中で反旗を翻す者が現れます｡
Also, in a short time,
someone within the human ranks
will incite a rebellion.
それは 誰かな？
And who would that be?
Jeanne D'Arc.
ジャンヌ･ダルクです｡
信じられないね｡
えっ…｡
That is hard to believe.
(ﾙｼﾌｪﾙ)何故 聖女が今更？➡
For what reason
would the saint do that?
それに 彼女は
その力を失って久しいとも聞く｡
Besides, I had heard that she
lost her powers long ago.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)あの女は 必ず
シャリオスを討ちに出ます｡
I can assure you, that woman
will strike out against Charioce.
(ﾙｼﾌｪﾙ)それが本当だとしても
確かな勝算がなければ➡
Even if that were true,
I cannot go to war with the humans
without some assurance of victory.
人との戦はできない｡
ルシフェル様｡
Lucifer!
僕らは 一度 負けているんだ｡➡
We have already lost once.
それを忘れてはいけない｡
We must not forget that.
ルシフェル様｡ 聖女の息子が➡
Lord Lucifer!
The saint's son
was killed by Charioce!
シャリオスの策に殺されたのです｡
あの女は 必ずや➡
That woman will bring the gods and humans--
神と人を従え…｡
誰が殺されようが関係ないよ｡
It doesn't matter who gets killed.
今は 静観することだけが➡
We only need to watch from a distance
to ensure our survival.
生き長らえるために必要なことだ｡
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)なっ…｡
Lucifer!
ルシフェル！
(ﾙｼﾌｪﾙ)ん？
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
いつまでも ビビってんじゃねぇ｡
When are you going to stop being a coward?
You are overstepping your bounds, Azazel.
言葉が過ぎるよ アザゼル｡
あんたが逃げ回ってる間も➡
While you were running away,
俺は 悪魔が殺され続けるのを
ずっと見てきた｡
I've had to watch demons be killed.
後先考えずに
ここを飛び出した君だって➡
But you weren't able to save them either
彼らを救うことは
できなかっただろう｡
after you rushed out of here without thinking.
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)
だが 一人戦う道を選んでも➡
But I was able to survive,
despite choosing to fight alone.
俺は生き長らえた｡ 逃げ隠れ➡
It's time you stop running and hiding,
just waiting to die!
ただ 死を待つのは もうやめろ！
生きるために 動きだすのは今だ！
Now's the time to take action to live!
バキッ！
(ｱｻﾞｾﾞﾙ)ぐわっ！
That is punishment for your insolence.
無礼な口を利いた罰だ｡➡
Will the saint really take action?
本当に聖女は動くのか？
Please believe me.
俺を信じてください｡
Assemble all the demons!
(ﾙｼﾌｪﾙ)全魔族を招集するんだ｡
口だけじゃないところを
見せてもらうよ｡
You will have to show me
that you are more than just talk.
I will.
ガチャ(ﾄﾞｱの開閉音)
(２人)うわっ！
Look at this mess!
ああ～ もう
また散らかしてるよ～｡
ほらほら
邪魔だから 出てった 出てった！
Now come on, get out!
You're in my way.
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)バカ野郎｡ あっ… ああ～！
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワァ～！➡
Idiot, what are you--
いや～ ひどい扱いですね｡
How could she treat us like that?
Why is she so energetic?
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)あいつは
なんで あんなに元気なんだ？
(ﾘﾀ)あの子 最近
暇さえあれば掃除してんのよね｡
Lately, she's been spending
all of her spare time cleaning.
はぁ…｡
なんで すぐ散らかすかなぁ｡
Why do they always make such a mess?
I wonder why I ever thought Mugaro was a girl.
私 なんで ムガロちゃんのこと
女の子と間違えたんだろう｡
ダン！
うっ… うぅ… ううっ！
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワァ…｡
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)ん？
≪コツ コツ コツ
なかなか
いい泣きっぷりだったぜ｡
That was a good cry.
本当なの？
ん？ 何がだ｡
Is it true?
Is what true?
本当に王様が ムガロちゃんを…｡
Did the king really do that to Mugaro?
分からねぇ｡
I don't know.
王様は これからも命を奪うの？
そうかもしれねぇ｡
Is the king going to take more lives?
He might.
王様は 私のことも…｡
そうかもしれねぇが➡
Does the king want me--
He might!
But we don't know anything for sure.
本当のことは 何も分からねぇ｡
カァー カァー…
腹減ってんだろ？ 今 リタが…｡
You've gotta be hungry.
Rita will...
If he's going to keep taking the
lives of the people I care about,
これ以上 あの人が➡
私の大切な人たちの命を
奪うなら➡
then I will stop him.
私が絶対に止める｡
止めるって お前 どうすんだよ？
Stop him?
How?
As horrible as you are
I can't help but love you
Even while I waited
That is all I felt
Ephemeral lovers, both flawed and missing pieces
We have finally become one
in this miniature garden at the edge of sorrow
Can you hear my heart speaking?
Ah, I may no longer feel
that I want to go back in time
But there are feelings, feelings, feelings
I can only feel now
I want to run away with you, dancing
just like in a fairy tale
Don't tell me it will only be this once, darling
I am on the same ark
Sha-ra-ran-la, Sha-ra-ran-la
Yeah
Cinderella step
Sha-ra-ran-la, Sha-ra-ran-la
Yeah
Cinderella step
Are you really going?
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)本当に行くのか？
まあな｡ エイボスには何かある｡
Yeah, there's something going down in Eibos.
昔 よく分からねぇ実験も
されたしな｡
Not to mention all the weird experiments
they've done there.
(ﾃﾞｨｱｽ)王が かの地で
何をしているか不明だが➡
We do not know the king's purpose
for visiting there,
危険だぞ｡
んなこたぁ分かってるっつぅの｡
-but it will be dangerous.
-I know that already.
だけど しょうがねぇだろ｡
But what other choice do I have?
どうしても
王様んとこに行きてぇんだと｡
She said she had to see the king.
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッ クワッ クワッ｡
ありゃ てこでも動かねぇ｡
There's no stopping her now.
(ﾘﾀ)ねえ ニーナ
無理すんじゃないわよ｡
Hey, Nina.
Take it easy.
はぁ…｡ あんたたち！
ちゃんとニーナを見張ってんのよ！
You guys better keep a close eye on Nina!
(ﾊﾞｯｶｽ)お… おう｡
(ﾊﾝｻ)クワッケイ｡
-Yeah, we will.
-Okay!
(ｶｲｻﾞﾙ)我々は王都に残り➡
We will stay in the capital and prepare for
whatever Jeanne and Azazel have planned.
ジャンヌ様とアザゼルの動向に
備える｡
おう｡
All right.
≫(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇの声)
我が名はジｬンヌ･ダルク｡
My name is Jeanne D'Arc.
(ｼﾞｬﾝﾇ)
大天使ガブリエル様の力により➡
Through the power of the archangel Gabriel
ミスタルシアに生きる
全ての者に伝える｡➡
I bring this message
to all beings of Mistarcia.
私は シャリオス１７世の暴挙を
決して許さない｡➡
Charioce XVII's reckless acts of violence
cannot be forgiven.
狂王に従う者 その全てを討伐し➡
I vow to strike down all who serve the mad king
この地に 真の平穏を
もたらすことを約束する｡
and bring true peace to these lands.
虐げられし者たちよ
２つの月が重なるとき➡
Those who have suffered by his hands,
when the two moons align,
武器を取り
イーディスの丘へと集え｡➡
take up arms and assemble at Edith's hill.
Now is the hour for rebellion!
今こそ 反逆のときだ｡
どうやら 君の言っていたことは
本当みたいだね｡
It seems like you spoke the truth.
Looks like we don't have any time to waste.
のんびりしてらんなそうだな｡
急ごう エイボスへ｡
Let's hurry to Eibos.
-It's Lucifer.
-This is Azazel.
We're the Fallen Angel Brothers.
-Don't use a book to hit someone.
-Sorry for hitting.
Next time on Rage of Bahamut:
Virgin Soul, "Which Way Is the Wind Blowing?"
Kids, do not use a book to hit someone.
-I am a demon.
-Sure you are.
BAHA SOUL
Baha Baha Baha Soul.
Please watch next time baha.